http://www.thealmanac.net/site/privacy.html

Upper St Clair
The Almanac, a publication of Observer Publishing Co., and thealmanac.net strive to offer visitors to our site a personal Internet experience, and to do this, we may from time to time ask for or use information such as your name, e-mail address, street address, telephone number, or certain demographic information subject to the terms of this privacy policy. This policy applies to information collected online and is not applicable to information collected or used by Observer Publishing Co. or thealmanac.net through other means.Requests for information.The nature of the information we might collect and the way in which we gather and store it depends on the web page that you are visiting or the services or activities you select on those pages. For example, you may be asked to provide appropriate information when you register for access to certain portions of our site, participate in forums, subscribe to the newspaper, request an archive reproduction, or use certain features. No information that identifies you personally will be gathered unless you are afforded the opportunity to refuse to provide such information.Automatic TrackingWhile thealmanac.net does log certain tracking information in ways transparent to visitors, this is not information that personally identifies any visitor. Examples are recording a visitor's Internet service provider or tracking the number of pages visited. We may use cookie technology to recognize someone on a subsequent visit. You can choose not to provide us with such information by setting your browser to refuse cookies, but that may render you unable to access certain portions of the site.What we do with information.We collect information to enhance your visit and may use it to deliver individualized content and/or advertising. We may sometimes permit advertising and/or promotional affiliates to call to your attention certain products, offers and web content. Information gathered on thealmanac.net will not be used to enable direct communications sent by our advertisers or promotional partners unless you are offered the opportunity to elect not to receive such direct communications.Aggregated InformationInformation that does not personally identify you may be used to enhance our site and services. For example, we may combine information about your usage patterns with similar information from other users to determine which pages are visited most or what features are most popular. Such information may be shared with advertisers and business affiliates, but only if it does not include any information to identify you individually.Affiliated sites, linked sites and advertisementsBe aware that third parties, including our advertisers, affiliates and others whose content may be accessible through thealmanac.net may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices. During your visit to our site you may link to or view certain content that is created or hosted by a third party. You should check the applicable privacy policies of those parties when providing information to them.Non-requested InformationIf you voluntarily disclose information on message boards or in chat areas, that information may be viewed publicly and can be collected and used by third parties without our knowledge and outside the control of thealmanac.net or this policy.ChildrenObserver Publishing Co. and thealmanac.net do not knowingly collect personal information from or about children under 15 except as permitted by law. If we discover we have received any information from a child under 15 in violation of this policy, we will delete that information. If you believe thealmanac.net has any information from or about anyone under 15, please contact us at the address listed below.Contacting usWe can be reached by contacting: Digital Services
Observer Publishing Co.
122 S. Main St.
Washington, PA 15301
Email: webmaster@observer-reporter.comImplied acceptance and changes to this policyContinued use of thealmanac.net constitutes acceptance of this policy and any changes that may from time to time be posted. Observer Publishing Co. reserves the right to change this policy at any time, but information collected prior to the posting of any change will be used only according to rules or laws in effect at the time the information was collected.Compliance with lawIt is the intent of Observer Publishing Co. that this privacy policy and operations of thealmanac.net shall comply with applicable laws of the Commonwealth of Pennsylvania and the United States of America. This statement and policies herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party. No other portion of this policy withstanding, we may disclose personal information if we are required to do so by law or we in good faith believe that such action is necessary to comply with the law; protect our rights and property; protect against misuse or unauthorized use of thealmanac.net; or protect the safety or property of our users or the public.
© Copyright 2020 The Almanac, 122 S. Main St Washington, PA | Terms of Use | Privacy Policy
